{
    "subject": "resource/Kung_Tsui-chang",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/Taiwan",
    "human_readable": "Kung Tsui-chang was born in Taiwan.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.954242467880249,
            "question": "Is Kung Tsui-chang from Taiwan?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9493420124053955,
            "question": "If Kung Tsui-chang was born in Taiwan, what language(s) might he speak?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9383925199508667,
            "question": "Where was Kung Tsui-chang born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9162304401397705,
            "question": "Kung Tsui-chang's birth location is Taiwan. What can you infer about his cultural background?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.773332953453064,
            "question": "Can you tell me Kung Tsui-chang's place of birth?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7557137608528137,
            "question": "What country is associated with Kung Tsui-chang's birthplace?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7444602847099304,
            "question": "What is the nationality of Kung Tsui-chang based on his birthplace?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7367140650749207,
            "question": "Where did Kung Tsui-chang originate from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6486738920211792,
            "question": "Taiwan is mentioned in relation to Kung Tsui-chang. What does this imply?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.48188352584838867,
            "question": "Which country holds significance in Kung Tsui-chang's early life?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Kung Tsui-chang was born in Taiwan.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8105_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Taiwan is mentioned in relation to Kung Tsui-chang. What does this imply?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8105_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where did Kung Tsui-chang originate from?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8105_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the nationality of Kung Tsui-chang based on his birthplace?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8105_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8105_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8105_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8105_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8105_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8105_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8105_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8105_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8105_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8105_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8105_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nThe reason for this answer is that according to the documents, Kung Tsui-chang was born in Australia (not Taiwan). The relevant sentence from one of the documents is:\n\n\"This year in Taipei, Kung Tsui-Chang returns to Taiwan from college in Australia with an ancient purpose.\""
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about Kung Tsui-chang, including his birth and role. While the specific mention of where he was born is not directly stated, it can be reasonably inferred from the context that he was born in Taiwan given his role as Sacrificial Official to Confucius in the Republic of China (Taiwan) and other details provided."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "The context information does not mention the birthplace of Kung Tsui-chang, but only mentions his birthdate (1 July 1975) and other details about him. However, it also includes a separate part that describes Chang Tung-Chia(Tung-Jia), who was born in Kaohsiung City, Taiwan, which implies that there might be another person named Kung Tsui-chang or this name is associated with someone else, but not the context of the main topic.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}